Huh?
Earthquake!
Only the essentials.
Essential?
>> Hey.
>> Essential?
No. What happened? Where'd you go? Huh?
Phew, we survived.
Hey, do you hear that?
Huh? What's going on out there? Could
you put me down?
What?
>> What?
>> What's happening here?
>> What are they building?
>> I spy these many code violations.
>> Hey, YOU THERE. WHO ARE YOU GUYS? WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> WE DIDN'T DO IT.
>> THIS is a construction zone. The city
has ordered us to put a new cell phone
tower at this location.
>> But we live here. Uh could you like move
it SOMEWHERE ELSE?
>> SORRY, BOSS. I accidentally made another
hole.
>> It's okay, Paul. We all make mistakes.
>> Listen, we received no record that
someone lives here.
>> But but this is our home. Wait, look.
We've welcome mat. See?
>> Welcome.
>> Whoops, made another hole.
>> Sorry, but you're going to need more
proof than that.
>> Well, then we'll get proof. You'll see.
>> Okay, we just need to know what counts
as good enough proof.
Okay, here we are. How about
>> Ooh ooh, click on that.
>> Home damage. Home damage caused in the
event we claim your home is unoccupied
can be easily corrected. Simply show a
copy of the deed or any other physical
evidence that shows five or more years
of presence. Once shown, we will
completely back off. Promise.
>> I liked that it was a cartoon.
>> We've totally been here longer than
that. I'm sure we have something from 5
years ago.
>> Okay, you go stall the construction.
Panda, you and me will find proof.
Break.
Got to be something around here.
No. Ooh.
>> Grizz, I found old stuff.
>> NO? NOPE. WOAH, this is from forever
ago, back when we first came to the
city. Hey, I remember this.
>> Well, here it is, the penthouse.
>> Whoa, this is massive.
>> Oh, this is crazy.
>> Ice Bear has never seen a larger
playpen.
>> Ooh, sounds like it's bigger than your
last place.
>> Oh, yeah, for sure.
>> We just moved here to the city.
>> That's wonderful. Where were you guys
living before?
>> A cardboard box.
>> [laughter]
>> That's funny.
>> Hi.
>> What's up, bro?
>> What's up?
>> So, this is the kitchen. You'll see it's
already furnished. And here we have the
deluxe industrial refrigerator.
And this is the hidden loft. It comes
with the best connection to our
building's newly installed internet
lines.
>> Dibs.
>> I love this place. It's everything we've
ever dreamed of. We'll take it.
>> Well, this is all great. I'll get
started on the paperwork. You'll be able
to move in as soon as we get first
month's rent.
>> Actually, we can pay right now. Uh looks
like I have about $11.
>> I have 76 cents.
>> Ice Bear has recyclable bottle.
>> Let's just open this.
>> HEY, YOU SHOULD GET OUT OF HERE. It's
not safe. Quick, move. Move.
Oh, got it.
>> Okay, not that many papers in here.
>> Hmm, is this trash?
>> Those are help, but it's not trash.
>> What's this?
>> Don't throw that away.
>> I wish you didn't hold on to so much.
>> Is this a bill?
>> No, just credit card application.
Probably save it for later, you know.
>> Do we save any of our bills?
>> Do we pay our bills?
>> Huh?
>> No.
No. No. No. No. No.
>> Sorry. We have to clear space.
>> HEY, STOP THAT.
>> SO, if I see any weird business, I kick
you out, okay?
>> That's great. We can't wait to see the
place.
>> If rent late one day, I kick you out,
okay?
>> Okay.
>> YOU, I SEE YOU. I KICK YOU OUT.
I FIX THAT DOOR, OKAY?
I kick out cat if you don't like. So,
you like?
>> I don't know about this.
>> I cool, man.
>> This is like the only place we could
afford.
>> What's wrong?
>> [music]
>> I swear we'll wait outside.